var questions = [{
		"question": " 10 : 10 = ...",
		"option1": "0",
		"option2": "1",
		"option3": "20",
		"answer": "2"
 }, {
		"question": " 25 + 13 = ...",
		"option1": "40",
		"option2": "28",
		"option3": "38",
		"answer": "3"
}, {
		"question": " 8 x 2 = ...",
		"option1": "16",
		"option2": "10",
		"option3": "6",
		"answer": "1"
}, {
		"question": " 3 + 3 = ...",
		"option1": "8",
		"option2": "6",
		"option3": "4",
		"answer": "2"
}, {
		"question": " 13 + 2 = ...",
		"option1": "11",
		"option2": "15",
		"option3": "17",
		"answer": "2"
}, {
		"question": " 10 - 4 = ...",
		"option1": "6",
		"option2": "4",
		"option3": "3",
		"answer": "1"
}, {  
		"question": " 2 + 8 = ...",
		"option1": "16",
		"option2": "6",
		"option3": "10",
		"answer": "3"
}, {
		"question": " 12 + 12 = ...",
		"option1": "32",
		"option2": "22",
		"option3": "24",
		"answer": "3"
}, {
		"question": " 4 x 3 = ...",
		"option1": "10",
		"option2": "15",
		"option3": "12",
		"answer": "3"
}, {
		"question": " 25 : 5 = ...",
		"option1": "5",
		"option2": "15",
		"option3": "10",
		"answer": "1"
}]